Anthony F. C. Wallace Papers 1920-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.64a
American Philosophical Society
- Series XII. Graphics, 9 linear feet
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Churches and jail, ca. 1984; 9 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Dormer's Tavern, ca. 1983; 2 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Maps, four views, 1864-1895; 4 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Monuments (Soldiers' Monument), ca. 1984; 1 item
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Monuments, ca. 1983; 3 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Parades, three views, ca. 1910; 4 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Parades, ca. 1910; 2 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Postcard with view of town, ca. 1910; 1 item
    Original envelope stated from Robert Scherr.
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Rohrig House, ca. 1983; 2 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Souvenir booklet with street scenes, ca. 1940; 1 item
    "Souvenir Letter, St. Clair, Pa." Souvenir booklet with green cover and eight black and white photographic images
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- St. Boniface Roman Catholic Church, ca. 1983; 1 item
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Street scenes, two views, ca. 1900; 3 items
    Second Street and Hancock Street, apparently enlarged from much smaller images, very blurred and grainy
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Street scenes, ca. 1983; 10 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Street scenes, ca. 1983; 14 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Street scenes, ca. 1983; 10 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Test sheet for book printing, ca. 1978; 1 item
    Transparency of page
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Town views, three images, 1873, n.d.; 4 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Town views, ca. 1940; 2 items
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.) -- Welsh Baptist Church
  - St. Clair (Schuykill County, Pa.), ca. 1983; 9 items
  - Thailand -- Chittibhol, Bancha: Home and family, 1965-1968; 11 items
  - Thailand -- Chittibhol, Bancha: Home and family, 1965-1968; 12 items
  - Thailand -- Chittibhol, Bancha: Home, family, and ancestors, 1890-1920; 7 items
  - Thailand -- Chittibhol, Bancha: Portuguese postcards, ca. 1967; 16 items
  - Thailand -- Postcards: Statues, ca. 1965; 5 items
  - Thailand -- Postcards, 1965-1967; 18 items
  - Thailand -- Postcards, 1965-1967; 17 items
  - Thailand -- Religious ceremony and family, ca. 1965; 11 items
    Religious ceremony that includes couple kneeling before altar; images of aunts holding children.
  - Thailand -- Religious ceremony, 1965, n.d.; 2 items
    Appears to be explanation of family relationships, illustrated in the photos in 4 x 5 and 5 x 7 boxes.
  - Thailand -- Thai bungalow and surroundings, ca. 1966; 8 items
  - Tuscarora Indians -- Anthony Wallace with Nellie Gansworth and Dan Smith, 1948; 1 item
  - Tuscarora Indians -- Rickard, Clinton in Indian dress, ca. 1948; 1 item
  - Tuscarora Indians -- Tuscarora Reservation, automobile with small blond boy on running board and two images of baby on blanket, one blurred, 1948; 8 items
  - Tuscarora Indians -- Tuscarora Reservation, Dan Smith, group of chiefs, and small girl, about age 5, four images, 1948; 5 items
  - Tuscarora Indians -- Tuscarora Reservation, four images (young couple, small girl about age 3, 1948; 10 items
  - Tuscarora Indians -- Tuscarora Reservation, surroundings and household tools, six images, 1948; 12 items
    Six images: gravel road in wooded area, dried-up stream bed, corn mortar and pestle, corn-washing basket, and baby board
  - University of Pennsylvania -- Faculty and staff, 1961; 1 item
  - Wadesville (Schuylkill County, Pa.) -- Silt dam, 1910; 1 item
  - Wallace Family -- Wallace children, Sun-Ai Kim in Korean and American dress, Betty, Monty and Daniel, 1959-1961; 8 items
  - Wallace Family (A.F.C.W., Betty, Dorothy, Sun-Ai, and Son-Wi), 1962; 7 items
    Anthony F.C. and Betty Wallace, two adopted Korean children Sun-Ai and Son-Wi and mother Dorothy (Clarke) Wallace
  - Wallace Family -- Wallace, Betty with Sun-Ai and Monty, 1961; 6 items
  - Wallace, Anthony F. C., 1923- -- Germany, 1945: Negatives, ca. 1945; 1 item
    Images include Café Fischer, soldier group
  - Wallace, Anthony F. C., 1923- -- Germany, 1945: Photographs, ca. 1945; 2 items
    Images include Café Fischer, two soldiers (one apparently Wallace)
  - Wallace, Anthony F. C., 1923- -- Portrait, 1961; 1 item
    Enlarged image of portrait in University of Pennsylvania, Faculty and Staff.
  - Wallace, Betty (Shillot) -- Betty Wallace with infant and Tuscarora Indian child Terri-Bear on reservation and in rocky area near Pine Forest stripping in Schuylkill County., ca. 1949, 1984
  - Wetherill, John Macomb -- Portrait, ca. 1870; 1 item
  - Yost, Benjamin -- Portrait, ca. 1870; 1 item
  - Iroquois cradleboard, 1937
  - Iroquois pictographs, 1956
  - Tuscarora man and woman, 1880?
  - Tuscarora woman, 1948